https://curbstone.com/privacy

COMPLIMENTARY NEEDS ANALYSIS:   CLICK HERE!
HomeProductsPartnersPrivacyiBlog
Print
Contents:
Data Privacy Notice
Online Privacy Notice
Data Privacy Notice
Includes California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (CCPA) Compliance
Curbstone facilitates credit card processing by linking merchants with whom you do business, and credit card authorization networks.  Curbstone therefore collects, processes, and/or stores the following categories of consumer personal information:  identifiers such as your name and address, email address, and account name; commercial information, specifically, credit card transaction data, including your credit card number, CVV number, and specific transaction details such as transaction amount, transaction date, and transaction merchant.  It obtains this data from merchants.  This data is collected, processed, and stored for the specific purpose of facilitating credit card processing between merchants and credit card authorization networks and settlements between them and their bank/acquirers.  This data is only shared with merchants, credit card authorization networks, and bank/acquirers, and only in accordance with Payment Card Industry-Data Security Standards (PCI-DSS), and applicable laws and regulations.
Residents of certain states have the right to request that their specific personal information that has been collected be disclosed to them by providing a request containing authenticating information.  Residents of certain states may also request that such personal information be deleted.  In order to safeguard your personal information, requests for disclosure or deletion must be properly authenticated before we are obligated to honor such request.  Moreover, any disclosure or deletion of personal information in response to an authenticated request is subject to, and will be made in accordance with, all applicable laws and regulations as well as Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards (“PCI-DSS”).  In certain circumstances, the applicable laws and regulations and PCI-DSS standards prohibit us from disclosing or deleting certain personal information.  In other cases, we are not required to comply with a deletion request if such deletion would prevent us from completing a transaction for which the personal information was collected, to provide goods or services you’ve requested, or to fulfill any contractual obligations between us and merchants, authorizing networks, or bank/acquirers in response to a transaction you’ve initiated.
California Residents Only - Effective only after January 1, 2020
California consumers have the following rights, subject to certain limitations and exclusions pursuant to the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA), Cal.Civ.Code § 1798.100 et.seq.:
the right to request disclosure of all personal information collected, sold, or disclosed for a business purpose
the right to request deletion of collected personal information, subject to certain limitations
the right to request that a business not sell their information (i.e. opt-out); and if the consumer does exercise their right to opt-out, Curbstone may not discriminate against that consumer as a result of their opting-out
To exercise these rights, a California consumer should submit a verified request at the following link
https://curbstone.com/contact
or call our toll-free number at
888-844-8533
Curbstone will ask for certain personal information in order to verify your identity before making any disclosure, or complying with any deletion or opt-out request in accordance with the CCPA.  As noted above, any request for deletion is subject to Curbstone’s compliance with applicable laws and regulations.  As shown in Table 1 below, Curbstone does not sell your personal information, so the CCPA’s opt-out mechanism does not apply to Curbstone.  Moreover, your request to opt-out could effectively negate your ability to complete any credit card transaction processed by Curbstone.
Curbstone’s disclosures regarding personal information pursuant to Cal.Civ.Code § 1798.115 are summarized in Table 1 below:
Category of personal information
Has Curbstone in the last 12 months done the following with consumer personal information…
Collected it?
Sold it?
Disclosed it for a business purpose?
Identifiers such as a real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, social security number, driver’s license number, passport number, or other similar identifiers.
Yes
No
Yes
Any categories of personal information described in subdivision (e) of Section 1798.80, i.e. any information that identifies, relates to, describes, or is capable of being associated with, a particular individual, including, but not limited to, his or her name, signature, social security number, physical characteristics or description, address, telephone number, passport number, driver's license or state identification card number, insurance policy number, education, employment, employment history, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information. “Personal information” does not include publicly available information that is lawfully made available to the general public from federal, state, or local government records
Yes
No
Yes
Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law.
No
No
No
Commercial information, including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies
Yes
No
Yes
Biometric information
No
No
No
Internet or other electronic network activity information, including, but not limited to, browsing history, search history, and information regarding a consumer’s interaction with an Internet Web site, application, or advertisement
No
No
No
Geolocation data
No
No
No
Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information
No
No
No
Professional or employment-related information
No
No
No
Education information, defined as information that is not publicly available personally identifiable information as defined in the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (20 U.S.C. section 1232g, 34 C.F.R. Part 99)
No
No
No
Inferences drawn from any of the information identified in this subdivision to create a profile about a consumer reflecting the consumer’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes
No
No
No
Table 1
End of Data Privacy Notice
Online Privacy Notice
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or Curbstone Corporation. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience -- (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To improve our website -- (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To improve customer service -- (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for any reason may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to our relationship, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from future emails, we include a simple unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. We use a secure server and all supplied information is transmitted via TSL technology. We do not collect or retain "sensitive" personal data.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our website's privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.  This policy was last modified on 09/04/2019
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, contact us using the information below.
https://curbstone.comCurbstone Corporation 201 Enterprise CourtBall Ground, Georgia 30107-6105info@curbstone.com888-844-8533
End of Online Privacy Notice
